class Data1 {
  List<Map> quizQuestions = [
    {
      'question': '1. Which motorcycle is Honda make?',
      'answers': ['Impulse', 'Boosa', 'Cbr', 'pulser'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 2, // cbr
    },
    {
      'question': '2. Who is the owner of TOYOTA?',
      'answers': ['Nick Bloor', 'Toshihiro Mibe', 'Ola Kallenius', 'Koji Sato'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 3, // koji sato
    },
    {
      'question': '3. Maruthi Swift model launching year?',
      'answers': ['2005', '2009', '2002', '1999'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, //2005
    },
    {
      'question': '4. Cubic capacity of RE Interceptor?',
      'answers': ['350', '650', '750', '500'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 1, // 650
    },
    {
      'question': '5. When was the motorcycles layout established?',
      'answers': [
        '1914',
        '1934',
        '1904',
        '1919'
      ],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // 1914
    },
    {
      'question': '6. CEO of Hero Honda?',
      'answers': ['Elon musk', 'Rathan tata', 'Vaniprabhu', 'Niranjan Gupta'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 3, // Niranjan Gupta
    },
    {
      'question': '7. Which car brand is known for producing\n Mustang models of cars?',
      'answers': ['Chevrolet', 'Ford', 'Dodge', 'Nissan'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 1, // Ford
    },
    {
      'question':
          '8. The headquarter of Audi is situated \n in which country?',
      'answers': ['U K', 'Germany', 'Austria', 'Switzerland'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 1, // Germany
    },
    {
      'question': '9.The "Cayenne" model of car is produced\n by which car manufacturer??',
      'answers': [
        'Porsche',
        'Bugatti',
        'Lamborghini',
        'Ferrari'
      ],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // porsche
    },
    {
      'question': '10. Aventador models are produced\n by which car brand?',
      'answers': ['Lamborghini', 'Porsche', 'BMW', 'Bugatti'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // lambo
    },
  ];
}
class Data2{
  List<Map> QuizQuestions = [
    {
      'question': '1.  Which of the following is not an SUV?',
      'answers': ['Carrera', 'Pajero', 'Range Rover', 'safari'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, //carrera
    },
    {
      'question': '2.  Which car brand produces the "Elantra" model??',
      'answers': ['Toyota', 'Maruthi', 'Mahhindra', 'Hyundai'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 3, // Hyundai
    },
    {
      'question': '3.Which car brand is known for producing Accord models of cars?',
      'answers': ['Suzuki', 'Honda', 'Mahindra', 'Tata'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 1, // honda
    },
    {
      'question': '4. What is the full form of ABS"?',
      'answers': ['Anti lock', 'All lock', 'All took', 'Access lock'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // anti lock
    },
    {
      'question': '5.Which of the following is a South Korean carmaker?',
      'answers': ['Mazda', 'Opel', 'Kia', 'Dodge'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 2, // kia
    },
    {
      'question': '6. Which company owns these brands: Bentley,Bugatti,Lamborghini,Audi??',
      'answers': ['Tata', 'Audi', 'Bens', 'Volkswagen'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 3, // volkswagen
    },
    {
      'question': '7.Double Wishbone is a type of _______?',
      'answers': ['Suspension', 'Engine', 'Tire', 'Brake'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // suspension
    },
    {
      'question': '8. Digital Twin Spark Ignition technology is patented by which company?',
      'answers': ['Tvs', 'Honda', 'Yamaha', 'Bajaj'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 3, //bajaj
    },
    {
      'question': '9. ceo of Yamaha?',
      'answers': ['Sundaram', 'Bavic Menon', 'Dis Cavel', 'Yoshihiro Hidaka'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 3, // Yoshihiro Hidaka
    },
    {
      'question': '10. Civic manufacterd ____?',
      'answers': ['Dodge', 'Honda', 'Tata', 'Toyota'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 1, // Honda
    },
  ];

}
class Data3{
  List<Map> QuizQuestions = [
    {
      'question': '1. The premium brand of toyota?',
      'answers': ['Dodge', 'Benz', 'Lexus', 'Ferrari'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 2, // Lexus
    },
    {
      'question': '2. Manufactering country of Ashok Leyland?',
      'answers': ['India', 'England', 'Italy', 'Saudi'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // india
    },
    {
      'question': '3.The first kerala registed Lamborgini owned?',
      'answers': ['Lal', 'Mammoty', 'Prithviraj', 'Soubin'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 2, // prithviraj
    },
    {
      'question': '4. Which bike is manufacterd Hero?',
      'answers': ['Star', 'Impulse', 'Gt', 'cbr'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 1, // impulse
    },
    {
      'question': '5. Safest car in the list?',
      'answers': ['volvo', 'Alto', 'Maruthi', 'Hm'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // volvo
    },
    {
      'question': '6. Which is off Roader?',
      'answers': ['Pulser', 'Rc', 'Duke', 'Himalayan'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 3, // Himalayan
    },
    {
      'question': '7. FF acter is ___?',
      'answers': ['Aaron paul', 'Paul walker', 'Captian', 'Restro'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 1, // paul
    },
    {
      'question': '8. The movie Ford vs Ferrari actor?',
      'answers': ['Shelby', 'Shellor', 'Graf', 'Novas'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Shelby
    },
    {
      'question': '9. Toyota manufacterd?',
      'answers': ['Alto', 'Brezza', 'Innova', 'Celerio'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 2, // innova
    },
    {
      'question': '10. Who is the ceo of Audi?',
      'answers': ['Gernot Dollner', 'Tokyo', 'MArs', 'Sepssr'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // GErnot
    },
  ];

}